seoconsultants.com 2005-12-30

# Privacy Policy - SEO Consultants Directory

We've created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website:

  * We do use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our websites.
  * This site contains hyperlinks to other websites of interest. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.
  * Our site uses multiple online forms for consumers and consultants to request various information about our services. We do collect visitor's contact information. The contact information is used to communicate with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving any future communication from us; see the choice/opt-out section below.

  * WebTrends Live is used to analyze traffic to this web site. WebTrends Live does not create individual profiles for visitors. Unlike some tracking services WebTrends Live does not have a database of individual profiles for each visitor. WebTrends Live only collects aggregate data.

More information about [WebTrends Live Privacy Policy](http://www.webtrendslive.com/wtl_system/privacy_policy.htm "More information about WebTrends Live Privacy Policy.").

## Internet Security

  * This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Such measures include password protected directories and other server related security implementation.

## Choice/Opt-Out

  * This web site gives users the following option for removing their information from our database and to not receive future communications from us.

[Please use our contact form for opt-out requests](https://www.seoconsultants.com/contact/ "Please use our contact form for opt-out requests.").

**Note:** We do maintain a contact database from those who have submitted information through our web sites. We do not send any unsolicited email for advertisements. We may decide in the future to send out an **SEO Consultants Newsletter** and will respectfully contact you **once** for your opt-in or opt-out, prior to including you on our list.

## Contacting the Owner of this Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact:

[Please use our contact form for general questions about this site](https://www.seoconsultants.com/contact/ "Please use our contact form for general questions about this site.").

Back to Previous

©2002-2006 [SEO Consultants Directory](http://www.seoconsultants.com/) | [Terms of Use](http://www.seoconsultants.com/legal/terms-of-use.asp) | [Privacy](http://www.seoconsultants.com/legal/privacy-policy.asp) | [About](http://www.seoconsultants.com/directory/about.asp) | [Contact](https://www.seoconsultants.com/contact/)  
All trademarks and servicemarks are the properties of their respective owners.

Last modified: 2005-11-24T13:27:40-0800
